800link.com 2019-03-29

# 800LiNK - Privacy Policy

Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website.

## Fundamental Principles

800Link, Inc. respects each individual's right to personal privacy. Here are a few fundamental principles we live by:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers any longer than we deem necessary to fulfill our obligations.

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that 800Link, Inc. ("800Link", "we", "our") treats the information you provide while using www.800Link.com ("Website"). It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

## Non-Personally Identifying Information

800Link collects non-personally identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. 800Link’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how 800Link’s visitors use its website. From time to time, 800Link may release non-personally identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

## Potentially Personally Identifying Information

800Link also collects potentially personally identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. 800Link only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally identifying information as described below.

## Personally Identifying Information

Certain visitors to 800Link’s website choose to interact with 800Link in ways that require 800Link to gather personally identifying information. The amount and type of information that 800Link gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with 800Link – by purchasing service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, 800Link collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with 800Link. 800Link does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

800Link may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its Website. For instance, 800Link may monitor the most popular content. 800Link may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, 800Link does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally Identifying Information

800Link discloses potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on 800Link’s behalf or to provide services available at 800Link’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using 800Link’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 800Link will not rent or sell potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, 800Link discloses potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when 800Link believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of 800Link, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an 800Link website and have supplied your email address, 800Link may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with 800Link. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or other feedback mechanism), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 800Link takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. 800Link uses cookies to help 800Link identify and track visitors, their usage of 800Link website, and their website access preferences. 800Link visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using 800Link’s website, with the drawback that certain features of 800Link’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Advertisements

Advertisements appearing on any of our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by 800Link and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site or its implementation you may contact us at support@800link.com.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, 800Link may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in 800Link’s sole discretion. 800Link encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Last updated Dec. 20, 2016
